<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="CBA_A3">
    <Package name="Disposable">
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_Component">
            <English>Community Base Addons - Disposable Weapons</English>
            <German>Community Base Addons - Einwegwaffen</German>
            <Japanese>Community Base Addons - 使い捨て武器</Japanese>
            <Czech>Community Base Addons - Jednorázové zbraně</Czech>
            <Turkish>Community Base Addons - Tek Kullanımlık Silahlar</Turkish>
            <French>Community Base Addons - Armes à usage unique</French>
            <Chinese>社群基礎模組 - 一次性武器</Chinese>
            <Russian>Community Base Addons - Одноразовое оружие</Russian>
            <Polish>Community Base Addons - Bronie jednorazowe</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropUsedLauncher">
            <English>Drop Used Disposable Launcher</English>
            <German>Benutzten Einwegwerfer ablegen</German>
            <Japanese>使った使い捨てランチャーを落とす</Japanese>
            <Czech>Odhodit použitý jednorázový raketomet</Czech>
            <Turkish>Kullanılan Tek Kullanımlık Roketleri At</Turkish>
            <Chinese>丟棄使用過的一次性發射器</Chinese>
            <French>Lâcher le lanceur usagé</French>
            <Russian>Выбрасывать использованный одноразовый гранатомёт</Russian>
            <Polish>Wyrzuć zużyty przedmiot</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropNever">
            <English>Never</English>
            <German>Niemals</German>
            <Japanese>行わない</Japanese>
            <Czech>Nikdy</Czech>
            <Turkish>Asla</Turkish>
            <Chinese>永不</Chinese>
            <French>Jamais</French>
            <Russian>Никогда</Russian>
            <Polish>Nigdy</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropNeverTooltip">
            <English>Don't automatically drop the used disposable launcher.</English>
            <German>Benutzten Einwegwerfer nicht automatisch ablegen.</German>
            <Japanese>使った使い捨てランチャーを自動的に落とさないようにします。</Japanese>
            <Czech>Automaticky neodhazovat použitý jednorázový raketomet.</Czech>
            <Turkish>Otomatik olarak tek kullanımlık roketleri atma.</Turkish>
            <Chinese>不要自動丟棄一次性使用之發射器</Chinese>
            <French>Ne lâche jamais automatiquement le lanceur usagé.</French>
            <Russian>Не выбрасывать автоматически использованный одноразовый гранатомёт.</Russian>
            <Polish>Nie wyrzucaj automatycznie wyrzutni.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropAIOnly">
            <English>AI Only</English>
            <German>Nur KI</German>
            <Japanese>AI のみ</Japanese>
            <Czech>Pouze AI</Czech>
            <Turkish>Sadece AI</Turkish>
            <Chinese>只有AI</Chinese>
            <French>IA seulement</French>
            <Russian>Только ИИ</Russian>
            <Polish>Tylko AI</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropAIOnlyTooltip">
            <English>Only AI drops the used disposable launcher.</English>
            <German>Nur KI legt den benutzten Einwegwerfer ab.</German>
            <Japanese>AI のみ使った使い捨てランチャーを落とすようにします。</Japanese>
            <Czech>Pouze AI odhodí použitý jednorázový raketomet.</Czech>
            <Turkish>Sadece yapay zeka tek kullanımlık roketleri atar.</Turkish>
            <Chinese>只有AI才會丟棄使用過的一次性發射器</Chinese>
            <French>Seules les unités IA lâchent leur lanceur après emploi.</French>
            <Russian>Только ИИ выбрасывает использованный одноразовый гранатомёт.</Russian>
            <Polish>Tylko AI wyrzuca wyrzutnie jednorazową.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropSelectedAnotherWeapon">
            <English>Selected Another Weapon</English>
            <German>Andere Waffe ausgewählt</German>
            <Japanese>別の武器が選択後</Japanese>
            <Czech>Vybrána jiná zbraň</Czech>
            <Turkish>Başka Bir Silah Seçince</Turkish>
            <Chinese>選擇其他武器</Chinese>
            <French>Si autre arme sélectionnée</French>
            <Russian>Выбрано другое оружие</Russian>
            <Polish>Wybierz inną Broń</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropSelectedAnotherWeaponTooltip">
            <English>Automatically drop the used disposable launcher as soon as another weapon is selected.</English>
            <German>Benutzten Einwegwerfer automatisch ablegen, sobald eine andere Waffe ausgewählt wurde.</German>
            <Japanese>他の武器を選択すると即時に使った使い捨てランチャーを自動的に落とすようにします。</Japanese>
            <Czech>Automaticky odhodit použitý jednorázový raketomet, jakmile je zvolena jiná zbraň.</Czech>
            <Turkish>Başka bir silah seçildiği zaman otomatik olarak tek kullanımlık roketleri at.</Turkish>
            <Chinese>當切換別的武器時自動丟棄一次性發射器。</Chinese>
            <French>Lâche automatiquement le lanceur usagé dès qu'une autre arme est sélectionnée.</French>
            <Russian>Автоматически выбрасывать использованный одноразовый гранатомёт, как только будет выбрано другие оружие.</Russian>
            <Polish>Automatycznie wyrzucaj wyrzutnie jednorazową  gdy tylko zostanie wybrana kolejna broń.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_ReplaceDisposableLauncher">
            <English>Replace Disposable Launcher</English>
            <German>Einwegwerfer ersetzten</German>
            <Japanese>使い捨てランチャーを置換</Japanese>
            <Czech>Vyměnit jednorázový raketomet</Czech>
            <Turkish>Tek Kullanımlık Roketleri Değiştir</Turkish>
            <Chinese>替換掉一次性發射器</Chinese>
            <French>Remplacer le lanceur à usage unique</French>
            <Russian>Заменять одноразовые гранатомёты</Russian>
            <Polish>Zamien wyrzutnie jednorazową</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_ReplaceDisposableLauncherTooltip">
            <English>If enabled, disposable launchers can only be used once. Ammunition for disposable launchers in containers and vehicles will be replaced with loaded disposable launchers. If disabled, disposable launchers can be reloaded after use.</English>
            <German>Wenn aktiviert, dann können Einwegwerfer nur einmal benutzt werden. Munition für Einwegwerfer in Kisten und Fahrzeugen wird durch geladene Einwegwerfer ersetzt. Wenn deaktiviert, dann können Einwegwerfer nach der Benutzung nachgeladen werden.</German>
            <Japanese>有効化すると、使い捨てランチャーは一度のみ使用できます。コンテナ内にある使い捨てランチャーは装填された使い捨てランチャーに置き換えられます。無効化すると、使用後に使い捨てランチャーをリロードできます。</Japanese>
            <Czech>Pokud je tato možnost zapnuta, jednorázové raketomety mohou být použity pouze jednou. Munice pro jednorázové raketomety v bednách a vozidlech budou vyměněny za nabité jednorázové raketomety. Pokud je tato možnost vypnuta, jednorázové raketomety mohou být přebity po použití.</Czech>
            <Turkish>Eğer bu ayar açıksa, tek kullanımlık roketler sadece bir kere kullanılabilir. Tek kullanımlık rokeyler için cephane başka tek kullanımlık roketler ile değiştirilir. Bu ayar kapalıyken tek kullanımlık roketler de birçok kez kullanılabilir.</Turkish>
            <Chinese>啟用時，將會把載具或容器裡面給於一次性發射器的彈藥換成一次性發射器本身，並且使其只能使用一次。如果關閉，一次性發射器即可再度裝填</Chinese>
            <French>Si activé, les lanceurs à usage unique ne peuvent être utilisés qu'une seule fois. Les munitions pour lanceurs à usage unique situés dans les conteneurs et les véhicules seront remplacées par des lanceurs à usage unique chargés. Si désactivé, les lanceurs à usage unique peuvent être rechargés après emploi.</French>
            <Russian>Если включено, одноразовые гранатомёты могут быть использованы лишь один раз. Боеприпасы для них в контейнерах и технике будут заменены на соответствующие им заряженные одноразовые гранатомёты. Если выключено, одноразовые гранатомёты могут быть перезаряжены и использованы повторно.</Russian>
            <Polish>Gdy ta opcja jest włączona wyrzutnie jednorazowe mogą być użyte tylko raz, Amunicja do wyrzutni jednorazowych dostępna w kontenerach i pojazdach zostanie zamieniona w załadowaną wyrzutnie jednorazową. Jeżeli ta opcja jest wyłączona, wtedy wyrzutnie jednorazowe nie zostaną przeładowane po użyciu.</Polish>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
