<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="CBA_A3">
    <Package name="Disposable">
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_Component">
            <English>Community Base Addons - Disposable Weapons</English>
            <Czech>Community Base Addons - Jednorázové zbraně</Czech>
            <French>Community Base Addons - Armes à usage unique</French>
            <Italian>Community Base Addons - Armi monouso</Italian>
            <Polish>Community Base Addons - Bronie jednorazowe</Polish>
            <Russian>Community Base Addons - Одноразовое оружие</Russian>
            <German>Community Base Addons - Einwegwaffen</German>
            <Korean>커뮤니티 베이스 애드온 - 일회용 무기</Korean>
            <Japanese>Community Base Addons - 使い捨て武器</Japanese>
            <Chinese>社群基礎模組 - 一次性武器</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>社群基础模组 - 一次性武器</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Community Base Addons - Tek Kullanımlık Silahlar</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropAIOnly">
            <English>AI Only</English>
            <Czech>Pouze AI</Czech>
            <French>IA seulement</French>
            <Italian>Solo AI</Italian>
            <Polish>Tylko AI</Polish>
            <Russian>Только ИИ</Russian>
            <German>Nur KI</German>
            <Korean>인공지능만</Korean>
            <Japanese>AIのみ</Japanese>
            <Chinese>只有AI</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>仅AI</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Sadece AI</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropAIOnlyTooltip">
            <English>Only AI drops the used disposable launcher.</English>
            <Czech>Pouze AI odhodí použitý jednorázový raketomet.</Czech>
            <French>Seules les unités IA lâchent leur lanceur après emploi.</French>
            <Italian>Solo le unità AI buttano il lanciatore usato.</Italian>
            <Polish>Tylko AI wyrzuca wyrzutnie jednorazową.</Polish>
            <Russian>Только ИИ выбрасывает использованный одноразовый гранатомёт.</Russian>
            <German>Nur KI legt den benutzten Einwegwerfer ab.</German>
            <Korean>인공지능만이 사용한 일회용 발사기를 떨어뜨립니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>AIのみが使用済の使い捨てランチャーを自動的に捨てるようにします。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>只有AI才會丟棄使用過的一次性發射器</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>只有AI会丢弃使用过的一次性发射器</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Sadece yapay zeka tek kullanımlık roketleri atar.</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropNever">
            <English>Never</English>
            <Czech>Nikdy</Czech>
            <French>Jamais</French>
            <Italian>Mai</Italian>
            <Polish>Nigdy</Polish>
            <Russian>Никогда</Russian>
            <German>Niemals</German>
            <Korean>없음</Korean>
            <Japanese>行わない</Japanese>
            <Chinese>永不</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>从不</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Asla</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropNeverTooltip">
            <English>Don't automatically drop the used disposable launcher.</English>
            <Czech>Automaticky neodhazovat použitý jednorázový raketomet.</Czech>
            <French>Ne lâche jamais automatiquement le lanceur usagé.</French>
            <Italian>Non buttare automaticamente il lanciatore usato.</Italian>
            <Polish>Nie wyrzucaj automatycznie wyrzutni jednorazowej.</Polish>
            <Russian>Не выбрасывать автоматически использованный одноразовый гранатомёт.</Russian>
            <German>Benutzten Einwegwerfer nicht automatisch ablegen.</German>
            <Korean>사용한 일회용 발사기를 자동으로 떨어뜨리지 않습니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>使用済の使い捨てランチャーを自動的に捨てないようにします。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>不要自動丟棄一次性使用之發射器</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>不自动丢弃使用过的一次性发射器。</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Otomatik olarak tek kullanımlık roketleri atma.</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropSelectedAnotherWeapon">
            <English>Selected Another Weapon</English>
            <Czech>Vybrána jiná zbraň</Czech>
            <French>Si autre arme sélectionnée</French>
            <Italian>Seleziona un'altra arma</Italian>
            <Polish>Wybierz inną Broń</Polish>
            <Russian>Выбрано другое оружие</Russian>
            <German>Andere Waffe ausgewählt</German>
            <Korean>다른 무기 선택</Korean>
            <Japanese>別の武器の選択後</Japanese>
            <Chinese>選擇其他武器</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>选择其他武器</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Başka Bir Silah Seçince</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropSelectedAnotherWeaponTooltip">
            <English>Automatically drop the used disposable launcher as soon as another weapon is selected.</English>
            <Czech>Automaticky odhodit použitý jednorázový raketomet, jakmile je zvolena jiná zbraň.</Czech>
            <French>Lâche automatiquement le lanceur usagé dès qu'une autre arme est sélectionnée.</French>
            <Italian>Butta automaticamente il lanciatore usato non appena un'altra arma viene selezionata</Italian>
            <Polish>Automatycznie wyrzucaj wyrzutnie jednorazową gdy tylko zostanie wybrana kolejna broń.</Polish>
            <Russian>Автоматически выбрасывать использованный одноразовый гранатомёт, как только будет выбрано другие оружие.</Russian>
            <German>Benutzten Einwegwerfer automatisch ablegen, sobald eine andere Waffe ausgewählt wurde.</German>
            <Korean>다른 무기를 선택하는 즉시 사용한 일회용 발사기를 자동으로 떨어뜨립니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>別の武器を選択すると即時に使用済の使い捨てランチャーを自動的に捨てるようにします。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>當切換別的武器時自動丟棄一次性發射器。</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>当切换其他武器时，就会自动丢弃使用过的一次性发射器。</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Başka bir silah seçildiği zaman otomatik olarak tek kullanımlık roketleri at.</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_DropUsedLauncher">
            <English>Drop Used Disposable Launcher</English>
            <Czech>Odhodit použitý jednorázový raketomet</Czech>
            <French>Lâcher le lanceur usagé</French>
            <Italian>Butta lanciatore usato</Italian>
            <Polish>Wyrzuć zużyty przedmiot</Polish>
            <Russian>Выбрасывать использованный одноразовый гранатомёт</Russian>
            <German>Benutzten Einwegwerfer ablegen</German>
            <Korean>사용한 일회용 발사기 떨어뜨리기</Korean>
            <Japanese>使用済の使い捨てランチャーを捨てる</Japanese>
            <Chinese>丟棄使用過的一次性發射器</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>丢弃使用过的一次性发射器</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Kullanılan Tek Kullanımlık Roketleri At</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_ReplaceDisposableLauncher">
            <English>Replace Disposable Launcher</English>
            <Czech>Vyměnit jednorázový raketomet</Czech>
            <French>Remplacer le lanceur à usage unique</French>
            <Italian>Sostituisci lanciatore monouso</Italian>
            <Polish>Zamien wyrzutnie jednorazową</Polish>
            <Russian>Заменять одноразовые гранатомёты</Russian>
            <German>Einwegwerfer ersetzten</German>
            <Korean>일회용 발사기 대체</Korean>
            <Japanese>使い捨てランチャーに置換</Japanese>
            <Chinese>替換掉一次性發射器</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>替换一次性发射器</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Tek Kullanımlık Roketleri Değiştir</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_CBA_disposable_ReplaceDisposableLauncherTooltip">
            <English>If enabled, disposable launchers can only be used once. Ammunition for disposable launchers in containers and vehicles will be replaced with loaded disposable launchers. If disabled, disposable launchers can be reloaded after use.</English>
            <Czech>Pokud je tato možnost zapnuta, jednorázové raketomety mohou být použity pouze jednou. Munice pro jednorázové raketomety v bednách a vozidlech budou vyměněny za nabité jednorázové raketomety. Pokud je tato možnost vypnuta, jednorázové raketomety mohou být přebity po použití.</Czech>
            <French>Si activé, les lanceurs à usage unique ne peuvent être utilisés qu'une seule fois. Les munitions pour lanceurs à usage unique situés dans les conteneurs et les véhicules seront remplacées par des lanceurs à usage unique chargés. Si désactivé, les lanceurs à usage unique peuvent être rechargés après emploi.</French>
            <Italian>Se abilitato, i lanciatori monouso possono essere usati una sola volta. Le munizioni per i lanciatori monouso che si trovano nei contenitori e nei veicoli saranno sostituiti con lanciatori monouso carichi. Se disabilitato, i lanciatori monouso possono essere ricaricati dopo l'uso.</Italian>
            <Polish>Gdy ta opcja jest włączona wyrzutnie jednorazowe mogą być użyte tylko raz, Amunicja do wyrzutni jednorazowych dostępna w kontenerach i pojazdach zostanie zamieniona w załadowaną wyrzutnie jednorazową. Jeżeli ta opcja jest wyłączona, wtedy wyrzutnie jednorazowe nie zostaną przeładowane po użyciu.</Polish>
            <Russian>Если включено, одноразовые гранатомёты могут быть использованы лишь один раз. Боеприпасы для них в контейнерах и технике будут заменены на соответствующие им заряженные одноразовые гранатомёты. Если выключено, одноразовые гранатомёты могут быть перезаряжены и использованы повторно.</Russian>
            <German>Wenn aktiviert, dann können Einwegwerfer nur einmal benutzt werden. Munition für Einwegwerfer in Kisten und Fahrzeugen wird durch geladene Einwegwerfer ersetzt. Wenn deaktiviert, dann können Einwegwerfer nach der Benutzung nachgeladen werden.</German>
            <Korean>활성화 시 일회용 발사기는 한번만 사용 가능합니다. 컨테이너와 차량에 담긴 일회용 발사기 탄약은 장전된 일회용 발사기로 대체됩니다. 비활성화 시 사용 후 일회용 발사기를 재장전할 수 있습니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>有効にすると、使い捨てランチャーは1回だけ使用できるようになります。 コンテナや車両に搭載されている使い捨てランチャーの弾薬は、装填済みの使い捨てランチャーに置き換えられます。 無効にすると、使い捨てランチャーは使用後にリロードできます。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用時，將會把載具或容器裡面給於一次性發射器的彈藥換成一次性發射器本身，並且使其只能使用一次。如果關閉，一次性發射器即可再度裝填</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>如果启用，一次性发射器将只能使用一次。库存和车辆中的一次性发射器的弹药将被替换为已装填的一次性发射器。如果禁用，一次性发射器在使用后可以重新装填。</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Eğer bu ayar açıksa, tek kullanımlık roketler sadece bir kere kullanılabilir. Tek kullanımlık rokeyler için cephane başka tek kullanımlık roketler ile değiştirilir. Bu ayar kapalıyken tek kullanımlık roketler de birçok kez kullanılabilir.</Turkish>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
